Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
GENIE, MAKE A WISH
يا جني، تمنى أمنية
- Someone's hacking the security system. - What do they want?
- أحدهم يخترق نظام الأمن. - ماذا يريدون؟
Who is it? Russia? Or North Korea?
من هي؟ روسيا؟ أم كوريا الشمالية؟
They're finding out now. We should rush over.
لقد اكتشفوا الأمر الآن. علينا أن نسارع.
SHOCK
صدمة
SEDUCTION
الإغواء
Sleep well?
نم جيداً؟
Let's kiss.
دعونا نقبل.
I need to plant onions.
أريد أن أزرع البصل.
Goodness me.
يا إلهي.
Done with the onions? Let's kiss.
انتهينا من البصل؟ هيا نتبادل القبلات.
Hold up. I left that thing back there. Silly me.
انتظر. تركتُ ذلك الشيء هناك. يا لي من غبي.
You came back for this coffin?
هل عدت من أجل هذا التابوت؟
- You've found it now, so let's kiss-- - Wait up. Stop.
- لقد وجدته الآن، فلنقبل... - انتظر. توقف.
This isn't something you can just do whenever, you know?
هذا ليس شيئًا يمكنك فعله في أي وقت، هل تعلم؟
You like rules, don't you?
أنت تحب القواعد، أليس كذلك؟
These things have rules too.
هذه الأشياء لها قواعد أيضاً.
- What are those rules? - Well, those rules are…
- ما هي تلك القواعد؟ - حسنًا، تلك القواعد هي...
First, the weather.
أولاً، الطقس.
Rain. It must be raining.
مطر.لا بد أن تمطر.
Not yesterday.
ليس بالأمس.
It was the first time yesterday.
لقد كانت المرة الأولى أمس.
First kisses tend to be
القبلات الأولى تميل إلى أن تكون
more spontaneous, less restricted by the rules.
أكثر عفوية، وأقل تقييدًا بالقواعد.
But it must be raining for the second one.
لكن لابد أن تمطر في المرة الثانية.
And there must be alcohol.
ويجب أن يكون هناك الكحول.
Just after a drink. Right then.
بعد شربة مباشرة.
It's that complex?
هل هذا معقد لهذه الدرجة؟
It's even more complex. I simplified it.
إنه أكثر تعقيدًا. لقد قمت بتبسيطه.
Now close this back up.
الآن قم بإغلاق هذه النسخة الاحتياطية.
You're really mixing identities like this?
هل أنت حقا تخلط الهويات بهذه الطريقة؟
The first digit has changed again.
لقد تغير الرقم الأول مرة أخرى.
That fucking psycho bitch.
تلك العاهرة المريضة اللعينة.
KI KA-YOUNG BALANCE: 20,688,348,652 WON
رصيد كي كا يونغ : 20,688,348,652 وون
And what's all this?
وما كل هذا؟
ESTIMATED ASSETS 4,300,431,074 WON
الأصول المقدرة 4,300,431,074 وون
MONTHLY BILL 34,074,250 WON
الفاتورة الشهرية 34,074,250 وون
CHEONGPUNGHO BANK
بنك تشيونغبونغو
LUNCH BREAK 12 P.M. TO 1 P.M.
استراحة الغداء من الساعة 12 ظهرًا إلى الساعة 1 ظهرًا
Ms. Gu, weren't you classmates with Ki Ka-young and Choi Min-ji?
السيدة جو، ألم تكوني زميلة في الدراسة مع كي كا يونغ وتشوي مين جي؟
- Yes. - Did you see their bags?
- نعم. - هل رأيت حقائبهم؟
They're both Hermès.
كلاهما هيرميس.
She's just letting it sit on the floor.
إنها فقط تتركه على الأرض.
Hey, could we get two iced Americanos?
مرحبًا، هل يمكننا الحصول على اثنين من أمريكانو المثلج؟
He always does that when we're headed to lunch.
إنه يفعل ذلك دائمًا عندما نتوجه لتناول الغداء.
You go ahead. I'll take a soybean paste stew.
تفضل، سأطلب حساء معجون فول الصويا.
You really should open a retirement savings fund account.
ينبغي عليك حقًا أن تفتح حسابًا لصندوق الادخار التقاعدي.
The earlier you plan for retirement, the better.
كلما خططت للتقاعد مبكرًا، كان ذلك أفضل.
I'm good. I don't need retirement.
أنا بخير. لا أحتاج إلى التقاعد.
What do you mean you don't need retirement?
ماذا تقصد بأنك لا تحتاج إلى التقاعد؟
It's just Ms. Ki prefers aggressive investments over low-risk ones.
إن السيدة كي تفضل الاستثمارات العدوانية على الاستثمارات منخفضة المخاطر.
Of course, I understand.
بالطبع، أنا أفهم.
We should give you our new towel sets. Ms. Gu? Where are they?
سنُهديكِ مجموعات مناشفنا الجديدة. آنسة غو؟ أين هي؟
Did you forget?
هل نسيت؟
Come on, Ms. Gu. You should take more initiative.
هيا يا آنسة جو، عليكِ المبادرة أكثر.
I'll bring them right over.
سأحضرهم على الفور.
Back to the topic of retirement, well…
بالعودة إلى موضوع التقاعد، حسنًا...
How should I explain this? The profitability…
كيف أشرح هذا؟ الربحية...
As of today, construction is complete. I just need a move-in date.
اليوم، اكتمل البناء. أريد فقط تحديد موعد للانتقال.
Do you like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
Yes, Dad.
نعم يا أبي.
Daddy!
بابي!
Goodness, you're blinding me!
يا إلهي، أنت تبهرني!
My darling princess, did you study hard today?
عزيزتي الأميرة هل درست بجد اليوم؟
Like my life depended on it. I'm tired as hell.
وكأن حياتي تعتمد على ذلك. أنا متعب للغاية.
I was paired up with the transfer student today.
لقد تم إقراني مع الطالب المنقول اليوم.
- And? - He's really cute.
-و؟ - إنه لطيف حقًا.
He is? Did he become the apple of your eye, Princess?
هو؟ هل أصبح قرة عينك يا أميرة؟
He seems really classy.
يبدو أنيقًا جدًا.
- So I asked where he lived. - And?
- فسألته أين يسكن. - و؟
- He lives in the mansion we talked about. - Over there?
- هو يعيش في القصر الذي تحدثنا عنه. - هناك؟
- Yeah. - They moved in?
- نعم. - انتقلوا للعيش هنا؟
If they've moved in, they should at least say hi.
إذا انتقلوا للعيش معنا، فيجب عليهم على الأقل قول مرحباً.
Guess we'll have to make a house call.
أعتقد أننا سنضطر إلى إجراء زيارة منزلية.
Open up!
افتح!
Wait, those rules
انتظر، تلك القواعد
were this accurate?
هل كان هذا صحيحا؟
Genie, tell me about tomorrow's weather.
يا جنى، أخبرني عن الطقس غدًا.
Why would you ask me?
لماذا تسألني؟
Weather is a touchy subject for me right now!
الطقس هو موضوع حساس بالنسبة لي الآن!
Why are you making such a fuss when I asked Genie?
لماذا أحدثت كل هذه الضجة عندما سألت الجني؟
Genie, so what's the weather like tomorrow?
يا جنى، كيف سيكون الطقس غدًا؟
It's set to be a clear and sunny day in Cheongpung tomorrow.
من المتوقع أن يكون الطقس غدًا صافيًا ومشمسًا في تشيونغ بونغ.
Hear that?
هل سمعت ذلك؟
You should try asking it something. It's so accurate.
يجب أن تحاول أن تسأله شيئًا ما. إنه دقيق جدًا.
Hey. Other Genie.
مرحباً، أيها الجني الآخر.
What does Ki Ka-young ask about the most?
ما هو الشيء الذي يسأل عنه كي كا يونغ أكثر؟
Here is a list of Ms. Ki Ka-young's recent search history.
فيما يلي قائمة بسجلات البحث الأخيرة للسيدة كي كا يونغ.
Rainmaking ritual, artificial rain, alcohol content of different beers,
طقوس صنع المطر، المطر الاصطناعي، محتوى الكحول في أنواع مختلفة من البيرة،
cool-toned lip tint, lightning-fast delivery,
لون شفاه بارد، توصيل سريع للغاية،
rainmaking ritual…
طقوس صنع المطر…
What the hell have you done, you idiot?
ماذا فعلت أيها الأحمق؟
Find out when it will rain this week.
تعرف على موعد هطول الأمطار هذا الأسبوع.
I just checked since the cherry blossom festival starts tomorrow.
لقد قمت بالتأكد من ذلك لأن مهرجان أزهار الكرز يبدأ غدًا.
Luckily, this entire week will be clear.
لحسن الحظ، سيكون هذا الأسبوع بأكمله صافياً.
Damn it, why?
لعنة عليك، لماذا؟
What about next week?
ماذا عن الاسبوع القادم؟
The spring rain hits next week, so Monday may be the only dry day.
من المتوقع هطول أمطار الربيع في الأسبوع المقبل، لذا قد يكون يوم الإثنين هو اليوم الجاف الوحيد.
- Monday will be dry? - Would you like it not to be?
- هل سيكون يوم الاثنين جافًا؟ - هل تريد أن لا يكون كذلك؟
You can do that?
هل يمكنك فعل ذلك؟
- Since you're a mythical beast? - I couldn't do it myself.
- بما أنك وحش أسطوري؟ - لم أستطع أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
But I can try praying.
ولكن يمكنني أن أحاول الصلاة.
Not exactly useful.
ليس مفيدًا تمامًا.
What is this about? Please put the wrench down.
ما هذا؟ أرجوك ضع المفتاح.
Is something there?
هل هناك شيء؟
I'm pretty today.
أنا جميلة اليوم.
Pretty.
جميل.
It's like the town is broke or something.
يبدو الأمر كما لو أن المدينة مفلسة أو شيء من هذا القبيل.
Why couldn't they get IU for the festival--
لماذا لم يتمكنوا من الحصول على IU للمهرجان--
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Put that down!
ضع ذلك!
I'm pretty.
انا جميلة.
Even prettier than before.
أجمل من ذي قبل.
Goodness, young lady.
حسنًا، يا آنسة.
There are mirrors all over this house!
هناك مرايا في جميع أنحاء هذا المنزل!
It's not your fault, Master.
إنه ليس خطؤك يا سيدي.
Psychopaths tend to be pretty narcissistic.
يميل المرضى النفسيون إلى أن يكونوا نرجسيين إلى حد كبير.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Thank goodness.
شكرا لله.
I thought I must have made her pretty somehow.
اعتقدت أنني ربما جعلتها جميلة بطريقة ما.
I was pretty awesome in the moment.
لقد كنت رائعاً جداً في تلك اللحظة.
Why did I pick that moment to get all competitive?
لماذا اخترت هذه اللحظة لأصبح تنافسيًا؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Now is the prime moment to get competitive.
الآن هو الوقت المناسب لتصبح أكثر تنافسية.
That kiss was the gateway to corruption.
وكانت تلك القبلة بوابة للفساد.
Right. It should be, but…
صحيح. ينبغي أن يكون كذلك، ولكن...
After 1,000 years,
بعد 1000 سنة،
it was practically my first kiss.
لقد كانت هذه قبلتي الأولى عمليًا.
I almost died from nerves.
لقد كاد أن يموت من التوتر.
I just feel bad for Ejllael.
أنا فقط أشعر بالأسف تجاه إجلائيل.
I hear he hits the gym nonstop because he wants to slit your throat.
سمعت أنه يذهب إلى صالة الألعاب الرياضية دون توقف لأنه يريد أن يذبحك.
Had he known a kiss would floor you, he could've avoided all that effort.
لو كان يعلم أن القبلة ستصيبك بالذهول، لكان بإمكانه تجنب كل هذا الجهد.
By the way, if it was your first in 1,000 years…
بالمناسبة، إذا كانت هذه هي المرة الأولى لك منذ 1000 عام...
Yeah, what?
نعم ماذا؟
Shouldn't you have gotten a dental scaling first?
ألا يجب عليك إجراء تنظيف الأسنان أولاً؟
Total jerk move.
حركة غبية تماما.
Dental scaling?
تنظيف الأسنان؟
What is that?
ما هذا؟
Raise your hand if you feel discomfort…
ارفع يدك إذا شعرت بعدم الراحة…
We haven't started yet.
لم نبدأ بعد
Say, "Ah."
قل "آه"
Bear with me for a moment.
تحملني للحظة.
You don't have any money?
ليس لديك أي أموال؟
And no ID?
ولا يوجد هوية؟
You treated him with no intake info?
لقد عالجته دون أي معلومات عن المدخول؟
He said that he's a friend of the auto shop owner, so…
قال إنه صديق لصاحب محل السيارات، لذا...
Ka-young? But I'm her only friend…
كا يونغ؟ لكن أنا صديقتها الوحيدة...
Wait, are you the guy from the…
انتظر، هل أنت الرجل من...
- Middle East? - Min-ji? I'm so happy to see you!
- الشرق الأوسط؟ - مين جي؟ أنا سعيدة جدًا برؤيتك!
I saw you eating gamja-tang together at the gamja-tang place!
لقد رأيتكما تأكلان غامجا تانغ معًا في مطعم غامجا تانغ!
Does seeing us eat gamja-tang together excuse you from paying?
هل رؤيتنا نأكل غامجا تانغ معًا تعفيك من الدفع؟
A tab?
علامة تبويب؟
Ridiculous, isn't it?
سخيف، أليس كذلك؟
It's outrageous, isn't it?
إنه أمر فظيع، أليس كذلك؟
Apparently, he doesn't have ID.
يبدو أنه لا يملك هوية.
And his name is none other than…
وإسمه ليس إلا…
Lee Beul-li.
لي بول لي.
That immediately killed my curiosity, so I stopped asking questions.
لقد قتل هذا فضولي على الفور، لذلك توقفت عن طرح الأسئلة.
Do you even know anything about this person?
هل تعرف أي شيء عن هذا الشخص؟
One thing I know for certain is that he isn't human.
الشيء الوحيد الذي أعرفه على وجه اليقين هو أنه ليس إنسانًا.
No, of course he isn't.
لا، بالطبع ليس كذلك.
No decent human racks up a tab with someone they just met.
لا يوجد إنسان محترم يدفع فاتورة لشخص التقى به للتو.
I'm feeling immense discomfort,
أنا أشعر بعدم ارتياح كبير،
so here are my hands.
وهنا يدي.
Seriously? I could just…
بجد؟ ممكن بس...
Dr. Choi, we need to get to the festival to volunteer.
الدكتور تشوي، نحن بحاجة للوصول إلى المهرجان للتطوع.
Okay. I'm coming.
حسنا. أنا قادم.
At this rate, you'll wind up in big trouble.
بالمعدل الحالي، سوف تقع في مشكلة كبيرة.
Snap out of it, Ms. Ki.
استيقظي من هذا، يا آنسة كي.
Okay, so he has a decent face, and he's pretty tall.
حسنًا، إذن لديه وجه لائق، وهو طويل القامة إلى حد ما.
And yeah, he has a velvety voice.
ونعم، لديه صوت مخملي.
Other than that, what's he got going for him?
وبخلاف ذلك، ما الذي لديه؟
It was essential given the rainy season.
كان ذلك ضروريا نظرا لموسم الأمطار.
I'll pay you back once I become a pro gamer…
سأعيد لك أموالك عندما أصبح لاعبًا محترفًا...
A pro gamer?
لاعب محترف؟
You've lost every game to the neighborhood kid.
لقد خسرت كل المباريات أمام الطفل المجاور لك.
Pro gamer, you say?
لاعب محترف، كما تقول؟
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
I dodged her pretty well today.
لقد تجنبتها بشكل جيد اليوم.
I was only hit on one side.
لقد أصبت في جانب واحد فقط.
What the heck?
ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
Ms. Ki.
السيدة كي.
Check the tire pressure for me, would you?
هل يمكنك التحقق من ضغط الإطارات بالنسبة لي؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
You're drinking.
أنت تشرب.
Yes, that I am.
نعم انا كذلك.
And you're at the wheel with the engine on.
وأنت على عجلة القيادة مع تشغيل المحرك.
Yes, I'm at the wheel.
نعم، أنا على عجلة القيادة.
Engine?
محرك؟
What's that?
ما هذا؟
All right, sir.
حسنا سيدي.
Blow into this for us.
انفخ في هذا من أجلنا.
And what's this? Is it a pipe?
وما هذا؟ هل هو أنبوب؟
Go on.
إستمر.
- Okay, more. - More.
- حسنًا، المزيد. - المزيد.
- Harder. - Harder!
- أصعب. - أصعب!
Hello, Homies! It's Da-jin of Sky Farm Life.
أهلاً يا جماعة! أنا دا-جين من سكاي فارم لايف.
I'm coming to you today from the Cheongpungho Cherry Blossom Festival.
أنا قادم إليكم اليوم من مهرجان أزهار الكرز في تشيونغبونغو.
Let's start off by raiding the For Daughter Strawberry stand.
دعونا نبدأ بمداهمة كشك For Daughter Strawberry.
Guys, what do you call a strawberry that was fired from its job?
يا شباب، ماذا تسمون الفراولة التي تم طردها من عملها؟
What?
ماذا؟
Berry upset!
التوت منزعج!
Right. "Berry upset!"
حَسَنًا. "بيري مُنْتَقِط!"
You're hilarious!
أنت مضحكة!
See that? Nothing flops for no reason.
هل ترى ذلك؟ لا شيء يفشل بدون سبب.
That was great.
ًكان كبيرا.
- Cherry blossoms! - Indeed.
- أزهار الكرز! - بالفعل.
Open wide. That's it.
افتح على مصراعيه. هذا كل شيء.
Can we try opening up a little wider?
هل يمكننا أن نحاول الانفتاح بشكل أوسع قليلاً؟
Even wider!
أوسع حتى!
Hello. We're from Cheongpungho Bank.
مرحباً، نحن من بنك تشيونغبونغو.
We have a savings event, so visit for a consultation.
لدينا حدث توفير، لذا قم بزيارتنا للحصول على استشارة.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Where is the bathroom?
أين الحمام؟
Is the subway station close by?
هل محطة المترو قريبة؟
Without cilantro, please.
بدون الكزبرة من فضلك.
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
Are you an Arab?
هل أنت عربي؟
You spoke Korean just fine earlier.
لقد تحدثت اللغة الكورية بشكل جيد في وقت سابق.
He doesn't want any cilantro.
إنه لا يريد أي كزبرة.
What?
ماذا؟
Arabic was big back in school, so I took it as my second language.
كانت اللغة العربية من أكثر اللغات انتشارا في المدرسة، لذا اعتبرتها لغتي الثانية.
I'll try speaking to him.
سأحاول التحدث معه.
My name is Oh Gyeong-yeol,
اسمي اوه كيونج يول
a police officer from the Republic of Korea.
ضابط شرطة من جمهورية كوريا.
Sir, you have violated the traffic laws--
سيدي، لقد خالفت قوانين المرور--
Get over here.
تعال إلى هنا.
You said speaking Arabic would work.
قلت أن التحدث باللغة العربية سوف يجدي نفعا.
About that. It worked for me toward the end of the Joseon dynasty…
بخصوص ذلك. لقد نجح الأمر معي في نهاية عهد جوسون...
Just go. I'll handle things here.
فقط اذهب، سأتولى الأمور هنا.
I could just…
أنا فقط أستطيع...
Oh Pan-geum!
أوه بان-جيوم!
Buy that to eat. That one.
اشتري هذا لتأكله. هذا.
Why are you walking around eating raw tofu?
لماذا تتجول وتأكل التوفو الخام؟
I hear this is post-police food.
سمعت أن هذا هو طعام ما بعد الشرطة.
Oh Pan-geum, you should drink some black goat extract.
أوه بان-جيوم، يجب عليك شرب بعض مستخلص الماعز الأسود.
To live a long life.
أن أعيش حياة طويلة.
I don't have that kind of money! Why don't you buy me one, then?
ليس لديّ هذا القدر من المال! لمَ لا تشتري لي واحدةً إذًا؟
I can't buy things for you. I only make recommendations.
لا أستطيع شراء أشياء لك. أنا فقط أقدم توصيات.
Honestly, I can't tell if you're a bastard or just pitiful.
بصراحة، لا أستطيع أن أقول إذا كنت لقيطًا أم مجرد شخص مثير للشفقة.
Goodness me.
يا إلهي.
- What? - Hey, would you look at that?
- ماذا؟ - مهلا، هل يمكنك أن تنظر إلى هذا؟
Goodness, that puppy is bouncing around on its own.
يا إلهي، هذا الجرو يقفز من تلقاء نفسه.
How incredible, no?
كم هو أمر لا يصدق، أليس كذلك؟
- Wow. What is this? - Come and have a look.
- واو. ما هذا؟ - تعالَ وانظر.
- How adorable! - It's walking!
- كم هو رائع! - ​​إنه يمشي!
It's so cool.
إنه رائع جدًا.
Hey, it's walking but still stays in the same spot.
مهلا، إنه يمشي لكنه لا يزال في نفس المكان.
How is that?
كيف ذلك؟
At least her joints seem strong.
على الأقل تبدو مفاصلها قوية.
My apologies.
اعتذاري.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
There's this thing called fireworks today. Do you know when and where?
هناك شيء اسمه الألعاب النارية اليوم. هل تعرف متى وأين؟
The fireworks? They'll be set off after the sun sets.
الألعاب النارية؟ سيتم إطلاقها بعد غروب الشمس.
You'd get the best view from there.
من هناك سوف تحصل على أفضل منظر.
Enjoy.
يتمتع.
The best view is that way?
أفضل منظر هو هذا الطريق؟
Ta-da.
نعم.
Damn, that fucker looked like he was loaded.
لعنة، هذا الوغد يبدو وكأنه كان محملاً.
But he was broke, damn it.
ولكنه كان مفلسًا، اللعنة.
Well, well. Look at these motherfuckers with no common decency.
حسنًا، حسنًا. انظروا إلى هؤلاء الأوغاد الذين لا يملكون أدنى أدب.
What do you think you're doing on our turf?
ماذا تعتقد أنك تفعل في ملعبنا؟
We thought we'd visit the cherry blossom festival.
لقد فكرنا في زيارة مهرجان أزهار الكرز.
The spring breeze is a-blowing.
نسيم الربيع يهب.
The cherry blossom festival is our turf.
مهرجان أزهار الكرز هو مجال عملنا.
We didn't go against the current to invade your cherry salmon festival, did we?
لم نذهب ضد التيار لغزو مهرجان سمك السلمون الكرزي الخاص بك، أليس كذلك؟
You could always come to next year's.
يمكنك دائمًا الحضور إلى العام المقبل.
What, should we send you an invite?
ماذا، هل يجب أن نرسل لك دعوة؟
Great, you should all get prosthetics while you're here.
رائع، يجب عليكم جميعًا الحصول على أطراف اصطناعية أثناء وجودكم هنا.
You know the health services in Cheongpung are first-class.
كما تعلم أن الخدمات الصحية في تشيونغ بونغ هي من الدرجة الأولى.
- What the… - What the heck?
- ماذا... - ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
What a relief! I almost got beat up by the lump of clay again.
يا له من ارتياح! كدتُ أتعرض للضرب من جديد بكتلة الطين.
And who's this prick?
ومن هذا الوغد؟
Hey, which gang are you from?
مهلا، من أي عصابة أنت؟
- What? - Why isn't he answering me?
- ماذا؟ - لماذا لا يجيبني؟
Just fucking wipe them all out!
فقط قم بمسحهم جميعا!
Darn it. I'm in the mood for flowers.
يا إلهي، أنا في مزاج للزهور.
- Damn you! - Hey, you bastard!
- اللعنة عليك! - يا أيها الوغد!
Wow.
رائع.
Goodness me.
يا إلهي.
Oh boy.
يا فتى.
How stunning.
كم هو مذهل.
AS SEXY FUCK YOU
مثير للغاية، اللعنة عليك
What the…
ماذا…
Goodness me, is that…
يا إلهي، هل هذا...
Is that my Ka-young's name up there?
هل هذا اسم كا يونغ الخاص بي هناك؟
"As, sexy, fuck, you"?
"كما، مثير، اللعنة، أنت"؟
Wait, what does that mean?
انتظر، ماذا يعني ذلك؟
So that prick does have money.
إذن هذا الوغد لديه المال.
KI KA-YOUNG YOU'RE IN MY HEART
كي كا يونغ أنت في قلبي
So women really love those words?
فهل النساء تحبن هذه الكلمات حقًا؟
Yes, I told you. Just trust me with these things.
نعم، قلت لك. فقط ثق بي في هذه الأمور.
They go absolutely wild.
إنهم يذهبون إلى البرية تماما.
She'll be corrupted in no time.
سوف يتم إفسادها في أي وقت من الأوقات.
Perfect.
ممتاز.
KI KA-YOUNG FUCK YOU
كي كا يونغ اللعنة عليك
That son of a gun.
هذا ابن البندقية.
That's what I always think when I see Iblis too.
هذا ما أفكر به دائمًا عندما أرى إبليس أيضًا.
I'm glad you relate, Ms. Ki Ka-young.
يسعدني أنك تتواصلين معي، السيدة كي كا يونغ.
What brings you here? You don't even have a car since you can fly.
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟ ليس لديك سيارة حتى وأنت قادر على الطيران.
Everyone in the village is at the festival.
الجميع في القرية موجودون في المهرجان.
I came as things are quiet.
لقد جئت عندما كان الوضع هادئا.
Do you have something to say to me?
هل لديك شيئا لتقوله لي؟
I won't return your feather.
لن أعيد لك ريشتك.
It's yours.
إنها لك.
What species are you, anyway?
ما هو نوعك، على أية حال؟
Just as there are Yorkshire terriers and Chihuahuas,
كما هو الحال مع وجود كلاب يوركشاير تيرير وتشيواوا،
there are humans, angels, devils, and genies. So which are you?
هناك بشر، وملائكة، وشياطين، وجن. فأيُّهم أنت؟
I'm obviously his servant. You saw my wings. I'm an angel.
أنا بالتأكيد خادمه. لقد رأيتَ جناحيّ. أنا ملاك.
Right, an angel?
صحيح ، ملاك؟
I thought I'd double-check since your wings were black.
اعتقدت أنني سأتحقق مرة أخرى لأن أجنحتك كانت سوداء.
You do volunteer lunch runs, right?
هل تقومين بجولات تطوعية لتناول الغداء، أليس كذلك؟
For a while, I've been thinking it's odd
لفترة من الوقت، كنت أعتقد أن الأمر غريب
how every time you deliver lunch, the elderly person
كيف في كل مرة تقوم فيها بتوصيل وجبة الغداء، يشعر الشخص المسن
ends up dead.
ينتهي به الأمر ميتًا.
I guess one could see it that way, but try switching the order of events.
أعتقد أنه يمكن رؤية الأمر بهذه الطريقة، ولكن حاول تبديل ترتيب الأحداث.
I visit dying elders to bring them peace.
أزور كبار السن المحتضرين لأحضر لهم السلام.
I see.
أرى.
One more thing.
شيئ آخر.
Several of your buildings are within a one-kilometer radius of my auto shop,
تقع العديد من المباني الخاصة بك ضمن دائرة نصف قطرها كيلومتر واحد من متجر السيارات الخاص بي،
and you never hid your identity from me.
ولم تخفي هويتك عني أبدًا.
Are you spying on me?
هل تتجسس علي؟
I am. To be more precise, I'm working on his orders.
أنا كذلك. لكي أكون أكثر دقة، أنا أعمل بناءً على أوامره.
What are they? His orders?
ما هي؟ أوامره؟
"If there comes a moment that Iblis bows his head before a human, you shall
"إذا جاءت لحظة ينحني فيها إبليس رأسه لإنسان، فعليك أن تطيعه".
slit your brother's throat."
"اقطع حلق أخيك."
Isn't that thrilling?
أليس هذا مثيرا؟
That's why I'm going to do my best to make sure Iblis doesn't win you over.
لهذا السبب سأبذل قصارى جهدي للتأكد من أن إبليس لن يكسبك.
It's too late.
لقد فات الأوان.
Pardon?
عفو؟
Get lost so I can close shop.
إذهب إلى الخارج حتى أتمكن من إغلاق المتجر.
Right.
يمين.
Is that the time?
هل هذا هو الوقت؟
But why are you being so rude?
ولكن لماذا أنت وقح جداً؟
Who knows? Maybe because psychopaths can't hide their displeasure?
من يدري؟ ربما لأن المرضى النفسيين لا يستطيعون إخفاء استيائهم؟
Or because you're trying to kill him when I'm his master?
أم لأنك تحاول قتله وأنا سيده؟
Or maybe because
أو ربما لأنه
he's already won me over.
لقد فاز بي بالفعل.
Which of these do you think it is?
أيهما تعتقد أنه هو؟
I knew I was right about her.
لقد عرفت أنني كنت على حق بشأنها.
A STUDY OF PSYCHOPATHS
دراسة عن المرضى النفسيين
Did something happen?
هل حدث شيء؟
- I brought the books-- - Throw them out again.
- أحضرت الكتب-- - ألقيهم خارجًا مرة أخرى.
Psychopath? I'm absolutely certain!
مختل عقليًا؟ أنا متأكد تمامًا!
I should've known it was too lucky.
كان ينبغي لي أن أعرف أن هذا كان محظوظا للغاية.
At this rate, there's no telling about her last two wishes.
بهذا المعدل، لا يمكن الجزم بشأن أمنياتها الأخيرتين.
Should I have taken my scythe with me?
هل كان ينبغي لي أن آخذ منجلي معي؟
She had the audacity to tell me to "get lost."
لقد كانت لديها الجرأة لتقول لي "أذهب إلى الخارج".
Like she was dismissing me!
كأنها كانت تطردني!
- To you, Master? - Yes.
- لك يا سيدي؟ - نعم.
You do look a little young for your age.
أنت تبدو أصغر سنا قليلا بالنسبة لعمرك.
Did you see the fireworks? Weren't they cool?
هل رأيتم الألعاب النارية؟ أليست رائعة؟
I did that, you know.
لقد فعلت ذلك، كما تعلم.
Why did you choose that…
لماذا اخترت ذلك…
Please, no!
من فضلك لا!
Hey, no using cheats like that!
مهلا، لا تستخدم الغش مثل هذا!
So you were behind the fireworks?
إذن أنت كنت وراء الألعاب النارية؟
Yes.
نعم.
I wondered which crazy fool was behind them.
لقد تساءلت من هو الأحمق المجنون الذي كان وراءهم.
Crazy what?
مجنون ماذا؟
Hey, where do you live? Lead the way, punk.
أهلاً، أين تسكن؟ قُد الطريق يا بانك.
And where do you live?
وأين تعيش؟
Lead the way.
قيادة الطريق.
Pardon?
عفو؟
The typical psychopath
المريض النفسي النموذجي
will harm others
سوف يؤذي الآخرين
to get what they want.
للحصول على ما يريدون.
But my dear Ka-young is a little different.
لكن عزيزي كا يونغ مختلف قليلاً.
Her grandma and the entire neighborhood rallied to raise her with hope,
لقد اجتمعت جدتها والجيران بأكملهم لتربيتها بالأمل،
so even though she may not feel guilt,
لذلك على الرغم من أنها قد لا تشعر بالذنب،
she knows to stay within her learned boundaries.
إنها تعلم أن تبقى ضمن حدودها التي تعلمتها.
All right. So what?
حسناً. ماذا إذن؟
So I'm saying I don't like you, you jerk.
لذا فأنا أقول أنني لا أحبك، أيها الأحمق.
Ka-young will stay within those boundaries no matter what,
سوف يبقى كا يونغ ضمن هذه الحدود مهما حدث،
and I will protect Ka-young as she does so.
وسوف أحمي كا يونغ أثناء قيامها بذلك.
Whether it be psychologically…
سواء كان ذلك نفسيا…
or physically.
أو جسديا.
I'm her knight in shining armor, you see.
أنا فارسها ذو الدرع اللامع، كما ترى.
You are, aren't you?
أنت كذلك، أليس كذلك؟
All this time, I thought you were a girl! Wow!
طوال هذا الوقت، كنت أعتقد أنك فتاة! واو!
This is on the house.
هذا على المنزل.
Why are you laughing?
لماذا تضحك؟
Funniest thing I've heard in 983 years.
أطرف شيء سمعته منذ 983 سنة.
Nine hundred and eighty…
تسعمائة وثمانون…
What the hell are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه بحق الجحيم؟
Now that we have a man in the mix, you come to a seafood stew joint?
الآن بعد أن أصبح لدينا رجل في المزيج، هل أتيت إلى مطعم يقدم حساء المأكولات البحرية؟
I can't believe you.
لا أستطيع أن أصدقك.
I didn't come. I just stopped by.
لم آتي، فقط توقفت.
I'll drop Min-ji off, so I'll see you at home.
سأوصل مين جي، لذا سأراك في المنزل.
Can't I take her home?
ألا يمكنني أن آخذها إلى المنزل؟
We've actually bonded. Honestly. Master?
لقد توطدت علاقتنا. بصراحة. يا سيدي؟
Just call me "ma'am."
فقط اتصل بي "سيدتي".
Do you need anything else?
هل تحتاج أي شيء آخر؟
Benevolence?
الإحسان؟
Min-ji didn't pay before she left, but I'm…
لم تدفع مين جي قبل أن تغادر، ولكنني...
I'm completely broke.
أنا مفلس تماما.
I know about that. Allow me.
أنا أعلم ذلك. اسمح لي.
I've reached 112, right?
لقد وصلت إلى 112، أليس كذلك؟
I'm turning myself in.
أنا أسلم نفسي.
Eating without paying? Seriously?
أكل بدون دفع؟ بجد؟
This is unfair. I didn't even eat. I just did the "not paying" part.
هذا ظلم. لم آكل حتى. لم أدفع إلا بعد أن تخلصت من العقاب.
Shut it.
أغلقها.
Why did you call me to bail you out?
لماذا اتصلت بي لانقاذك؟
What about the one who's like you? That angel!
ماذا عن الذي مثلك؟ ذلك الملاك!
You're mistaken about that.
أنت مخطئ في هذا.
Not only are Ejllael and I different species, we're on bad terms.
ليس فقط أن إجلائيل وأنا من نوعين مختلفين، ولكننا على علاقة سيئة.
You and I are also on bad terms.
أنت وأنا أيضا على علاقة سيئة.
What's with you lowering your voice?
لماذا تخفض صوتك؟
I may be Satan, but this is no laughing matter.
ربما أكون الشيطان، لكن هذا ليس بالأمر المضحك.
Ejllael and I fought a long battle.
لقد خاضت أنا وإجلائيل معركة طويلة.
The war was devastating for me too.
وكانت الحرب مدمرة بالنسبة لي أيضا.
Why did you go to war?
لماذا ذهبت إلى الحرب؟
He created angels from light
خلق الملائكة من نور
and genies from smokeless fire.
والجن من نار بلا دخان.
The genies created from fire grew increasingly arrogant,
أصبحت الجنيات التي تم خلقها من النار متغطرسة بشكل متزايد،
even aspiring to surpass Him.
بل ويطمح إلى التفوق عليه.
In his rage, he sent the angels and ordered them to decimate us.
وفي غضبه أرسل الملائكة وأمرهم بإبادةنا.
The angels came down and began slaughtering all the genies,
نزل الملائكة وبدأوا بذبح جميع الجن،
and Ejllael led the charge.
وتولى إجلائيل قيادة الهجوم.
The war lasted 300 years,
استمرت الحرب 300 سنة،
and I lost most of my brothers as a result.
وخسرت معظم إخوتي نتيجة لذلك.
So your quarrels turn into full-blown wars of the gods?
فهل تتحول خلافاتكم إلى حروب كاملة بين الآلهة؟
I've rarely seen my brothers since then.
نادرًا ما رأيت إخوتي منذ ذلك الحين.
Partly because I defied his orders and ended up in hell.
جزئيًا لأنني تحديت أوامره وانتهى بي الأمر في الجحيم.
And once released, I ended up trapped for almost 1,000 years, so there's that.
وبمجرد إطلاق سراحي، انتهى بي الأمر محاصرًا لمدة تقرب من 1000 عام، وهذا هو الأمر.
Where are your surviving brothers now?
أين إخوتك الباقين على قيد الحياة الآن؟
I'm not sure.
أنا لست متأكدا.
They're probably inhabiting rings or lamps
ربما يسكنون حلقات أو مصابيح
or living out their days in a pot.
أو يعيشون أيامهم في وعاء.
They may be controlling sleep…
قد يكونون هم المسيطرين على النوم...
or tending to the flowers of souls.
أو الاعتناء بزهور النفوس.
Or perhaps controlling the rain.
أو ربما السيطرة على المطر.
One controls the rain?
من يتحكم بالمطر؟
- What? - Can't you find him? Find him and--
- ماذا؟ - ألا تجده؟ ابحث عنه و-
Can't. No longer with us.
لا أستطيع. لم يعد معنا.
I think Sade is looking for me.
أعتقد أن ساد يبحث عني.
I'm pretty sure Sade isn't looking for you.
أنا متأكد من أن ساد لا يبحث عنك.
Wow.
رائع.
Miss, does the owner of this car live in this neighborhood?
سيدتي، هل صاحب هذه السيارة يعيش في هذا الحي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Must be a crypto bro.
يجب أن يكون تشفيرًا يا أخي.
I used to drive one of these.
لقد كنت أقود واحدة من هذه السيارات.
That's the 2024 model.
هذا هو نموذج 2024.
Hey, come on!
مهلا، هيا!
I said to patch the puncture, not take the tire off!
لقد قلت أن أقوم بإصلاح الثقب، وليس إزالة الإطار!
It needs to be changed.
يجب أن يتغير.
Did you even report all these? Every one of these modifications?
هل أبلغت عن كل هذه التغييرات؟
What are you, a civil servant? Why would I report anything?
ما أنت، موظف حكومي؟ لماذا أبلغ عن أي شيء؟
Hey, put it back on.
مهلا، ضعه مرة أخرى.
Where do you live?
أين تعيش؟
Why do you ask?
لماذا تسأل؟
Like what you see?
هل يعجبك ما ترى؟
Just concerned you'll croak on your way home.
أنا فقط قلق من أنك ستموت في طريقك إلى المنزل.
Did you do these wheels yourself?
هل قمت بعمل هذه العجلات بنفسك؟
You shoved them on when they don't even fit.
لقد دفعتهم عندما لم يكونوا مناسبين حتى.
A simple patch-up wouldn't last an hour.
لن يستغرق التصحيح البسيط ساعة واحدة.
I've explained everything, so call a tow truck and take it away.
لقد شرحت كل شيء، لذا اتصل بشاحنة سحب وأخذها بعيدًا.
I won't fix it.
لن اصلحه
Is this how you treat your customers? Hey, get over here.
هل هكذا تُعاملون زبائنكم؟ هيا، تعالوا إلى هنا.
Is everything good?
هل كل شيء جيد؟
You drank that?
شربت ذلك؟
There were so many bottles. Weren't they for staff?
كان هناك الكثير من الزجاجات. أليست مخصصة للموظفين؟
No wonder they kept going missing.
لا عجب أنهم ظلوا في عداد المفقودين.
Wait, what were you saying?
انتظر ماذا كنت تقول؟
I was just asking for the tow truck number.
كنت أسأل فقط عن رقم شاحنة السحب.
Zero, one, zero,
صفر، واحد، صفر،
six, three, four…
ستة، ثلاثة، أربعة…
- Wait, I didn't catch that. - Two…
- انتظر، لم أفهم ذلك. - اثنان...
Did you hit him?
هل ضربته؟
Six, three, four…
ستة، ثلاثة، أربعة…
What are you going to do about this random, dreamy vibe?
ماذا ستفعل بشأن هذا الشعور العشوائي والحالم؟
I'm sorry. I'll report everything.
أنا آسف. سأبلغ عن كل شيء.
- I swear. - Where are you going?
- أقسم. - إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
- Damn it. - Don't go.
- اللعنة. - لا تذهب.
Hello, ma'am.
مرحبا سيدتي.
- Hello. - Thank you. Feel free to browse.
- أهلاً. - شكراً لك. تفضل بالتصفح.
Who's in charge of this display?
من المسؤول عن هذا العرض؟
Who's responsible for this station?
من المسؤول عن هذه المحطة؟
Hey, you're back!
مهلا، لقد عدت!
I'm sorry, Im-seon.
أنا آسف، إم-سيون.
I had to step out for a moment. My bowels were acting up again.
اضطررتُ للخروج للحظة. عادت أمعائي إلى الاضطراب.
Don't you think it's wrong to call your branch manager by name?
ألا تعتقد أنه من الخطأ أن تنادي مدير فرعك باسمه؟
At our age, we're all a little unwell.
في سننا، نحن جميعا مريضون قليلا.
Is it too much to ask you to do your job?
هل من الصعب أن أطلب منك القيام بعملك؟
I can't take any more of this crap.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل المزيد من هذا الهراء.
Ms. Jung Yeong-sun. What did you just say?
آنسة جونغ يونغ سون، ماذا قلتِ للتو؟
I said I can't stand it anymore. This is so ridiculous that I quit.
قلتُ إنني لم أعد أتحمل هذا. هذا سخيفٌ جدًا لدرجة أنني توقفتُ.
Im-seon, this is just wrong.
إم سون، هذا خطأ تمامًا.
Has the late promotion gone to your head?
هل أثر الترقية المتأخرة على عقلك؟
Ms. Jung Yeong-sun!
السيدة جونغ يونغ سون!
I don't know how you were even promoted,
لا أعرف كيف تمت ترقيتك،
but is this how you treat your coworkers?
لكن هل هذه هي الطريقة التي تعامل بها زملاءك في العمل؟
We've all heard the rumors about you taking bribes from vendors.
لقد سمعنا جميعًا الشائعات حول حصولك على رشاوى من البائعين.
Do we look like fools?
هل نبدو كالحمقى؟
Yeong-sun, please!
يونغ سون، من فضلك!
How could I be so stupid?
كيف يمكنني أن أكون غبيًا جدًا؟
I shouldn't have asked to be a branch manager at this age.
لا ينبغي لي أن أطلب أن أكون مدير فرع في هذا العمر.
People look down on me, and I keep making mistakes.
الناس ينظرون إليّ بازدراء، وأنا أستمر في ارتكاب الأخطاء.
I guess I could get to it a bit quicker.
أعتقد أنني قد أتمكن من الوصول إليه بشكل أسرع قليلاً.
Excuse me?
اعذرني؟
Here's my second wish.
وهنا أمنيتي الثانية.
Take me back 20 years
خذني 20 عامًا إلى الوراء
and make me branch manager then.
واجعلني مديرًا للفرع بعد ذلك.
If I'd made branch manager back then, just imagine all the money.
لو كنت مديرًا للفرع في ذلك الوقت، فقط تخيل كل الأموال.
Shall we go, then? Twenty years into the past?
هل نذهب إذن؟ بعد عشرين عامًا؟
BRANCH MANAGER KANG IM-SEON
مدير الفرع كانغ إم سون
Go through that door, and it will be 20 years in the past,
مر من هذا الباب، وسوف يكون قد مضى 20 عامًا على ذلك.
and you will still be the branch manager.
وسوف تظل مديرًا للفرع.
Talk to me.
تحدث معي.
Why are you alone? Where's Dad? He said he'd pick you up.
لماذا أنت وحدك؟ أين أبي؟ قال إنه سيأخذك.
Dad has work to do.
أبي لديه عمل للقيام به.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
Do you still like hot chamomile tea?
هل لا تزال تحب شاي البابونج الساخن؟
Yes. I'm still a psychopath, so caffeine isn't good for me.
نعم. ما زلت مريضًا نفسيًا، لذا الكافيين ليس جيدًا لي.
You haven't changed a bit.
لم تتغير على الإطلاق.
I thought you'd at least ask, "What brings you here?"
اعتقدت أنك ستسأل على الأقل، "ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟"
I moved here with my wife and son.
انتقلت إلى هنا مع زوجتي وابني.
Take good care of us. I found out about this place thanks to you.
اعتني بنا جيدًا. بفضلك عرفتُ هذا المكان.
I don't recall ever telling you exactly where I live.
لا أذكر أنني أخبرتك على وجه التحديد بمكان إقامتي من قبل.
Not many University of Science grads run auto shops.
ليس هناك الكثير من خريجي جامعة العلوم الذين يديرون محلات تصليح السيارات.
I guess.
اعتقد.
Either way, it's good to see you again. You look great.
على أي حال، من الجيد رؤيتك مرة أخرى. تبدو رائعًا.
How's business?
كيف حال العمل؟
True joy.
الفرح الحقيقي.
I guess the house looked pretty much the same 20 years ago.
أعتقد أن المنزل كان يبدو بنفس الشكل تقريبًا قبل 20 عامًا.
Except for you.
إلا أنت.
You grow up to be super pretty 20 years from now.
ستصبحين جميلة جدًا بعد 20 عامًا من الآن.
So careful with this. You wouldn't want to hurt…
كن حذرًا جدًا في هذا الأمر. لن ترغب في إيذاء...
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Someone just entered my memory.
لقد دخل شخص ما إلى ذاكرتي للتو.
Grandma told me not to speak to strangers.
قالت لي جدتي أن لا أتحدث مع الغرباء.
Leave!
يترك!
Wait, no!
انتظر، لا!
Hey, you startled me.
مهلا، لقد فاجأتني.
So you're clearly as odd as ever.
فمن الواضح أنك غريب كما كنت دائمًا.
"So you're clearly as odd as ever."
"لذا من الواضح أنك غريب كما كنت دائمًا."
He was sleazy as hell.
لقد كان رخيصًا جدًا.
So how did you hurt your head again?
إذن كيف أذيت رأسك مرة أخرى؟
Who else would it be?
من سيكون غيره؟
She was even worse 20 years ago.
لقد كانت أسوأ قبل عشرين عامًا.
Did you visit the past for a wish?
هل زرت الماضي من أجل أمنية؟
Yeah.
نعم.
That'll be 18,000 won.
سيكون ذلك 18000 وون.
I need to see your ID for the alcohol…
أريد أن أرى هويتك للكحول ...
Ms. Ki!
السيدة كي!
What's wrong? Is something up?
ما الخطب؟ هل هناك شيء ما؟
Just that it's raining.
فقط أنه ممطر.
Keep up the good work.
استمر في العمل الجيد.
Where the hell is he?
أين هو بحق الجحيم؟
Wait, what?
انتظر ماذا؟
Why is it stopping?
لماذا يتوقف؟
But it's the rainy season!
لكن هذا موسم الأمطار!
Where the hell were you? It rained!
أين كنت بحق الجحيم؟ لقد أمطرت!
Do you know how long I looked everywhere for you?
هل تعلم كم من الوقت بحثت عنك في كل مكان؟
Seriously?
بجد؟
Hey, you're the one
مهلا، أنت الشخص المناسب
who took a rock this big, you know.
من أخذ صخرة بهذا الحجم، هل تعلم؟
You do all that, then I hear about you acting all "odd."
عندما تفعل كل هذا، أسمع عنك تتصرف بطريقة "غريبة".
You're deflecting because you're cornered.
أنت تنحرف لأنك محاصر.
I'm in a corner? Who was the jerk who came by the auto shop?
أنا في الزاوية؟ من هذا الأحمق الذي مرّ على ورشة السيارات؟
I heard you were giggling with each other.
سمعت أنكم كنتم تضحكون مع بعضكم البعض.
Kiss me or crack my skull, but just do one.
قبلني أو اكسر جمجمتي، ولكن افعل واحدة فقط.
You can't do both, you serial kisser!
لا يمكنك فعل الأمرين، أيها المقبِّل المتسلسل!
I can't?
لا أستطبع؟
Then I choose to crack your skull. Come here.
ثم قررت أن أكسر جمجمتك. تعال هنا.
Hey, come on. You're my master.
هيا، أنت سيدي.
Shush. We're talking right now.
ششش، نحن نتحدث الآن.
Come on. Treat me with care.
تعال.عاملني بعناية.
Take care of me.
اعتني بي.
I said shush!
قلت اسكت!
Why does every damn dog around here bark like mad whenever they see you?
لماذا ينبح كل كلب هنا بجنون عندما يراك؟
They're just scared I'll take them in.
إنهم خائفون فقط من أن آخذهم معي.
They need to read human expressions, but I don't have any.
إنهم بحاجة إلى قراءة التعبيرات الإنسانية، لكن ليس لدي أي منها.
Hey, I don't plan on taking you in either!
مهلا، أنا لا أخطط لأخذك أيضًا!
Sade!
قال!
I am Genie, the lamp spirit. …shall grant you three wishes…
أنا الجني، روح المصباح. ...سأمنحك ثلاث أمنيات...
…no traveling to the future.
...لا سفر إلى المستقبل.
Anything besides that,
أي شيء بخلاف ذلك،
your wish… is my command.
رغبتك... هي أمري.
But before that,
ولكن قبل ذلك،
tell all the dogs in the area to stop barking at Ki Ka-young.
أخبر جميع الكلاب في المنطقة بالتوقف عن النباح على كي كا يونغ.
If they bark one more time,
إذا نبحوا مرة أخرى،
I'll change every last one of you into cats.
سأقوم بتحويل كل واحد منكم إلى قطط.
Tell him.
أخبره.
Ki Ka-young.
كي كا يونغ.
MUTT, AGE 7 MADE FIRST WISH ON MAY 16, 2024
مات، البالغ من العمر 7 سنوات ، حقق أمنيته الأولى في 16 مايو 2024
TO BECOME A PERSON, WITH SPECIFICS
لتصبح شخصًا، مع تفاصيل
CHARMING MIDDLE-AGED MAN IN HIS 40S WHO RESEMBLES DANIEL HENNEY
رجل ساحر في منتصف العمر في الأربعينيات من عمره يشبه دانيال هيني
Now that's not a face you see in these parts.
هذا ليس الوجه الذي تراه في هذه الأنحاء.
Is there a film shoot?
هل يوجد تصوير فيلم؟
Remember I was depressed about losing my eyesight with age?
هل تتذكر أنني كنت مكتئبًا بسبب فقدان بصري مع تقدمي في السن؟
- Yeah? - I think I just fully recovered.
- نعم؟ - أعتقد أنني تعافيت تمامًا.
- Let's go, Yeong-sun. - Sure.
- دعنا نذهب، يونغ سون. - بالتأكيد.
Wow.
رائع.
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
Chicken and beer?
دجاج و بيرة؟
Sounds good. Let's do it.
يبدو جيدًا. لنفعل ذلك.
Suit and slicked back hair. Wow, he's doggone handsome.
بدلة وشعر مصفف للخلف. يا له من وسيم!
He's coming this way.
إنه قادم من هذا الطريق.
Hand me some blotting paper and lip tint.
أعطني بعض ورق النشاف وأحمر الشفاه.
- What's he doing? - He must be crazy!
- ماذا يفعل؟ - لابد أنه مجنون!
My gosh!
يا إلهي!
They say handsome men are either gay or dogs.
يقولون أن الرجال الوسيمين إما أن يكونوا مثليين أو كلاب.
His actions clearly show
أفعاله تظهر بوضوح
he's a total mutt.
إنه كلب هجين تماما.
You've run out of water.
لقد نفذ الماء منك.
Don't skip breakfast tomorrow.
لا تتخطى وجبة الإفطار غدًا.
Pardon?
عفو؟
The food doesn't taste good.
الطعام ليس طعمه جيدا.
It's too bland.
إنه ممل للغاية.
It's too bland for you?
هل هو ممل جدًا بالنسبة لك؟
I should have been more generous with the salt.
كان ينبغي لي أن أكون أكثر سخاءً مع الملح.
I was only joking.
لقد كنت أمزح فقط.
What will happen to me now?
ماذا سيحدث لي الآن؟
A question I'm tired of getting.
سؤال تعبت من الحصول عليه.
One thing's for certain.
هناك شيء واحد مؤكد.
I'll be saving on the cost of salt.
سأوفر في تكلفة الملح.
Yes, Grandma?
نعم جدتي؟
Ka-young, you're not seeing things again, are you?
كا يونغ، أنت لا ترى الأشياء مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
You're taking your meds, right? Every dose without missing any?
أنت تتناول أدويتك، صحيح؟ كل جرعة دون أن تفوت أي جرعة؟
Yes, you see me take them every day. Why?
نعم، تراني أتناولها كل يوم. لماذا؟
If you have any wishes, just tell me. I'll make them all come true.
إذا كانت لديك أي أمنيات، أخبرني بها. سأحققها لك جميعًا.
Wishes?
أمنيات؟
What is this in the notebook in your room?
ما هذا الموجود في دفتر الملاحظات الموجود في غرفتك؟
Did you like Daniel Henney?
هل اعجبك دانييل هيني؟
You can see that?
هل يمكنك رؤية ذلك؟
She can see that?
هل تستطيع رؤية ذلك؟
Wait, was it always visible to everyone else's eyes?
انتظر، هل كان دائمًا مرئيًا لأعين الجميع؟
You're seriously asking me that?
هل أنت جديا تسألني هذا السؤال؟
This damn magic has way too many holes.
هذا السحر اللعين لديه الكثير من الثغرات.
This won't do.
هذا لن يفعل.
We need a safe space to hide the notebook and pen.
نحن بحاجة إلى مكان آمن لإخفاء الدفتر والقلم.
Your lamp.
مصباحك.
Are you sure only you and Sade can get in?
هل أنت متأكد من أنك وساد فقط من يستطيع الدخول؟
If they really wanted to, Ejllael or Irem probably could.
لو أرادوا ذلك حقًا، فمن المحتمل أن يتمكن إجلائيل أو إيريم من ذلك.
But even you couldn't.
ولكن حتى أنت لم تستطع ذلك.
So it must be safe.
لذا يجب أن يكون آمنًا.
What does it look like inside the lamp? Is it cozy?
كيف يبدو داخل المصباح؟ هل هو مريح؟
It's dismal.
إنه أمر كئيب.
Do you see this?
هل ترى هذا؟
Do you get a sense of how lonely I must have been for 983 years?
هل لديك إحساس بمدى الوحدة التي شعرت بها لمدة 983 عامًا؟
Sorry, but I don't know what loneliness is.
عذرا ولكنني لا أعرف ما هو الشعور بالوحدة.
But you do know to be sorry?
ولكن هل تعلم أن تعتذر؟
Of course I don't.
بالطبع لا أفعل.
But Min-ji told me that leading with that makes me seem considerate.
لكن مين جي أخبرتني أن ذلك يجعلني أبدو مراعيًا.
And you know what considerate is?
و هل تعلم ما هو الاعتبار؟
Yes. That one's quite easy.
نعم، هذا سهل جدًا.
I just need to be honest. For instance, it's something like this.
أريد فقط أن أكون صادقًا. على سبيل المثال، الأمر كالتالي.
I heard it all from that brother of yours.
لقد سمعت كل ذلك من أخيك.
That you'll get your throat slit if you bow your head to a righteous human.
أنك ستتعرض للذبح إذا انحنيت برأسك لإنسان صالح.
Ejllael, that prick!
إجلائيل، هذا الوغد!
That was considerate? Not a threat?
هل كان ذلك مُراعيًا؟ ليس تهديدًا؟
Are you seriously not
هل انت جاد؟
scared of me?
خائفة مني؟
To be honest, I don't know what fear is.
بصراحة لا أعرف ما هو الخوف.
But Grandma did say that apathy is the scariest.
لكن جدتي قالت أن اللامبالاة هي الأكثر رعبا.
My grandma is an incredibly fragile safety feature to my apathy.
إن جدتي هي ميزة أمان هشة للغاية بالنسبة لعدم مبالاتي.
If that safety feature…
إذا كانت هذه ميزة الأمان...
were to disappear,
كان من المقرر أن تختفي،
there's a chance my violence would take over,
هناك احتمال أن يسيطر عنفي،
so I'm making preparations.
لذلك أنا أقوم بالتحضيرات.
But you'd know all that from spying on me.
لكنك ستعرف كل ذلك من خلال التجسس علي.
"As natural a death as possible."
"موت طبيعي قدر الإمكان."
I do know, yes.
أنا أعلم، نعم.
Like deep-sea equipment failure or a fall on a remote trail.
مثل فشل المعدات في أعماق البحار أو السقوط على درب بعيد.
But why do all that when you don't have emotions or any affection for humans?
ولكن لماذا تفعل كل هذا وأنت لا تملك أي مشاعر أو أي عاطفة تجاه البشر؟
I am a stone in a shoe to the people of the world.
أنا حجر في حذاء بالنسبة لشعوب العالم.
I make people uncomfortable.
أجعل الناس يشعرون بعدم الارتياح.
So I'm removing that stone for them.
لذلك سأقوم بإزالة هذا الحجر من أجلهم.
For my grandma.
لجدتي.
So if you're going to kill me, hurry. And don't go getting your throat slit.
لذا، إن كنت ستقتلني، فأسرع. ولا تُذبح.
Ejllael?
إجلائيل؟
The more I see that angel, the less I like him.
كلما رأيت هذا الملاك، كلما قل إعجابي به.
- Whatever you do, don't lose to him. - Wait, you're actually taking my side?
- مهما فعلت، لا تخسر أمامه. - انتظر، هل أنت في الواقع تقف إلى جانبي؟
- Shouldn't I? - You shouldn't. If you do, then…
- ألا يجب عليّ؟ - لا يجب عليكِ. إذا فعلتِ، إذًا...
You know?
أنت تعرف؟
I'm going to wring
انا سأعصر
your neck.
رقبتك.
That would make things strange.
وهذا من شأنه أن يجعل الأمور غريبة.
We're already strange.
نحن غريبون بالفعل.
You and I are both antisocial,
أنت وأنا كلاهما غير اجتماعيين،
so why am I under scrutiny while you're admired?
فلماذا أنا تحت التدقيق بينما أنت تحظى بالإعجاب؟
What exactly was his purpose in making you and me meet?
ما هو هدفه بالضبط من جعلك وأنا نلتقي؟
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
I should have been pondering that.
كان ينبغي لي أن أفكر في ذلك.
Not totally clueless.
ليس جاهلاً تمامًا.
Okay, we need furniture.
حسنًا، نحن بحاجة إلى أثاث.
Bring over the table and chairs I made in the workshop.
أحضر الطاولة والكراسي التي صنعتها في الورشة.
No matter which way I look at it,
بغض النظر عن الطريقة التي أنظر بها إلى الأمر،
I don't think you made these.
لا أعتقد أنك قمت بذلك.
They seem to be made by a giant corporation.
يبدو أنها مصنوعة من قبل شركة عملاقة.
Don't talk back! You now have two pieces of furniture.
لا ترد! لديك الآن قطعتان من الأثاث.
It'd be nice to have another rug, wouldn't it?
سيكون من الجميل أن يكون لدينا سجادة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
This way. Here.
من هنا. هنا.
Starting the cleaning cycle.
بدء دورة التنظيف.
Why the hell is this…
لماذا هذا الجحيم...
Is this used to fix things or to destroy them?
هل يستخدم هذا لإصلاح الأشياء أم لتدميرها؟
That all depends on you.
هذا كله يعتمد عليك .
Hey!
يا!
Go that way, and you won't come back. It'd take over 1,000 years.
اسلك هذا الطريق ولن تعود. سيستغرق الأمر أكثر من ألف عام.
That thing.
هذا الشيء.
It's coming together.
إنه قادم معًا.
Now I feel somewhat reassured.
الآن أشعر بالاطمئنان إلى حد ما.
About Ms. Im-seon.
نبذة عن السيدة إيم سون.
She could have done whatever she wanted beyond the supermarket,
كان بإمكانها أن تفعل ما تريد خارج السوبر ماركت،
so I wonder why she didn't just leave the supermarket.
لذلك أتساءل لماذا لم تغادر السوبر ماركت.
That's how humans are.
هكذا هم البشر.
They dream of being king but fear leaving their domain.
إنهم يحلمون بأن يصبحوا ملوكًا ولكنهم يخافون من مغادرة نطاقهم.
They've seen how kings rule by force, and so they wish for the same.
لقد رأوا كيف يحكم الملوك بالقوة، ولذلك يتمنون الشيء نفسه.
That's the cowardly nature of humans
هذه هي طبيعة البشر الجبانة
and the reason why I hate them.
والسبب الذي يجعلني أكرههم
He may not be clueless, but he's also not big on enlightenment.
قد لا يكون جاهلاً، لكنه أيضًا ليس من محبي التنوير.
Humans hate you too.
البشر يكرهونك أيضًا.
So that's another use for that.
إذن هناك استخدام آخر لذلك.
If I killed you on behalf of all humans, would I go to heaven?
إذا قتلتك نيابة عن جميع البشر هل سأذهب إلى الجنة؟
You think it would end at that?
هل تعتقد أن الأمر سينتهي عند هذا الحد؟
He'd give you heaven if you asked.
سيعطيك الجنة إذا طلبت ذلك.
Come here. Get over here.
تعال هنا. تعال هنا.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Get over here.
تعال إلى هنا.
- I said come. - I don't want to.
- قلت تعال. - لا أريد.
I LAUGH IN MY DREAMS, JOYFULLY
أضحك في أحلامي بفرح
- Let's keep it humane and… - But you're not human.
- دعونا نحافظ على الإنسانية و... - ولكنك لست إنسانًا.
Where is that mumbling coming from?
من أين يأتي هذا التذمر؟
I can hear sound coming from this. Is it a radio?
أسمع صوتًا قادمًا من هنا. هل هو راديو؟
Pan-geum!
جوهرة!
Pan-geum, are you home?
بان-جيوم، هل أنت في المنزل؟
Yes, I'm here!
نعم انا هنا!
Goodness, you came all this way in the pouring rain?
يا إلهي، لقد قطعت كل هذه المسافة تحت المطر الغزير؟
I think she said…
أعتقد أنها قالت...
it's raining.
إنها تمطر.
It seems that way, doesn't it?
يبدو الأمر كذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Do you have any alcohol here?
هل يوجد لديكم أي كحول هنا؟
Should I buy some?
هل يجب علي أن أشتري بعضًا منها؟
Wouldn't it be faster…
ألا سيكون ذلك أسرع؟
to go together?
لنذهب معا؟
Don't forget we need money to buy alcohol.
لا تنسوا أننا نحتاج إلى المال لشراء الكحول.
- This is all I need. - You'll use that as collateral?
- هذا كل ما أحتاجه. - هل ستستخدم ذلك كضمان؟
- My goodness. What shall we do? - Grandma?
يا إلهي. ماذا نفعل؟ - جدتي؟
Grandma, why are you crying?
جدتي لماذا تبكي؟
- Good heavens. - What is it?
- يا إلهي. - ما الأمر؟
Why is she crying?
لماذا تبكي؟
We just heard that the craftsman, Mr. Kim, died.
سمعنا للتو أن الحرفي السيد كيم قد توفي.
You know, the man who taught you how to carve wood.
هل تعلم، الرجل الذي علمك كيفية نحت الخشب.
Then why is my grandma crying?
إذن لماذا تبكي جدتي؟
She's crying because she's sad.
إنها تبكي لأنها حزينة.
She's sad that her friend died.
إنها حزينة لأن صديقتها ماتت.
This is exactly why, you know.
وهذا هو السبب بالضبط، كما تعلمون.
Why people call you a psycho.
لماذا يطلق عليك الناس لقب مريض نفسي؟
Heung-rye!
هيونغ راي!
What?
ماذا؟
Goodness me!
يا إلهي!
Death makes life seem so futile.
الموت يجعل الحياة تبدو تافهة.
It brings me to tears.
إنه يجعلني أبكي.
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
It's so tragic. I can't bear it.
إنه أمر مأساوي للغاية. لا أستطيع تحمله.
How can you cast the world aside like this?
كيف يمكنك أن تتخلى عن العالم بهذه الطريقة؟
Even so, they say he passed peacefully as if drifting off to sleep.
ومع ذلك، يقولون أنه توفي بسلام وكأنه كان ينام.
Consider that a good death.
اعتبر ذلك موتًا جيدًا.
There's no such thing as a good death.
لا يوجد شيء اسمه موت جيد.
I guess you kids would have no idea, with your entire lives ahead of you.
أعتقد أنكم يا أطفال ليس لديكم أي فكرة، مع حياتكم بأكملها أمامكم.
I'm not afraid of dying,
أنا لا أخاف من الموت،
but if I think of my darling Ka-young…
ولكن إذا فكرت في حبيبتي كا يونغ...
What if my heart suddenly stops
ماذا لو توقف قلبي فجأة؟
or I have a stroke and collapse?
أو أصاب بجلطة دماغية وأنهار؟
What if I get cancer and diabetes and end up with dementia too?
ماذا لو أصبت بالسرطان والسكري وانتهى بي الأمر بالإصابة بالخرف أيضًا؟
Good heavens, how would she ever take care of me?
يا إلهي، كيف لها أن تعتني بي؟
Why would you think such silly thoughts?
لماذا تفكر بمثل هذه الأفكار السخيفة؟
At that moment, I realized that Grandma must have read the same articles as me.
في تلك اللحظة أدركت أن جدتي لابد وأن قرأت نفس المقالات التي قرأتها.
"An aging society is coming fast."
"إن المجتمع المتقدم في السن قادم بسرعة."
"Prepare yourself for age-related illness."
"أعدّ نفسك للأمراض المرتبطة بالعمر."
"Medical Tomorrow."
"الغد الطبي"
I was going to die if Grandma died,
كنت سأموت إذا ماتت جدتي،
but Grandma actually wants
لكن الجدة تريد ذلك فعلا
to live a long and healthy life.
لعيش حياة طويلة وصحية.
So your point is?
فما هي وجهة نظرك؟
I'll make my second wish.
سأحقق أمنيتي الثانية.
Make my grandma young.
اجعل جدتي شابة.
The same age as me.
نفس عمري.
This is my second wish.
هذه هي أمنيتي الثانية.
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi
ترجمة الترجمة بواسطة: جيمين تشوي